https://www.spwhsl.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – The Spinning Wheel Sleuth
Skip to navigation
Skip to content
Search for:
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for The Spinning Wheel Sleuth (spwhsl.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, forms, orders, purchases, or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.
Sharing and Credit Card Processing
We use an outside credit card processing company (PayPal) to bill users for goods and services. You can consult their privacy policy for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. The Spinning Wheel Sleuth‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other web sites.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Log Files
Like many other web sites, The Spinning Wheel Sleuth makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
The Spinning Wheel Sleuth uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information about which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
Third Party Privacy Policies
You should consult the respective privacy policies of any third-party sites for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. The Spinning Wheel Sleuth‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity. The Spinning Wheel Sleuth does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that The Spinning Wheel Sleuth has in its database the personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact at the end of this document) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Your Access to and Control over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the form below:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by using the form below.
Update
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, May 11, 2018.
Should we update, amend, or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
Contact The Spinning Wheel Sleuth About Our Privacy Policy
Please enable JavaScript in your browser to complete this form.Your Name *Your Email *Your message *GDPR Agreement *I consent to having this website store my submitted information so they can respond to my inquiry.WebsiteSend Message
Sources: San Francisco BBB, PrivacyPolicyOnline.com
Most Recent Issue and Supplement
Issue #109 – July 2020
• Tension Systems on Great Wheels• The Bedwell Wheels of Tennessee• A "Granny Greer Wheel"• Restoring a "Log Top" Double-Flyer Wheel
Hand Loom Supplement #21 – April 2019
• Gallinger Loom Design• The Sears Hearthside Looms• Nellie Sargent Johnson: Creator of the Sears Hearthside Looms• Inga Askling and Her Two-Legged Loom• The Loom in a Wallace Nutting Photograph
See all Issues or Supplementscurrent
issue
supplement
© The Spinning Wheel Sleuth
Privacy Policy
My Account
Search
Search for:
Search
0
0
Your Cart
